One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
The Counterattack Begins!
One of the Seven Warlords of the Sea, Trafalgar Law.
A pirate recently reported to have made a full comeback, Straw Hat Luffy,
and his crewmate, Devil Child Nico Robin.
The Navy's own wild dog, White Hunter Smoker.
How did Caesar ever manage to get a lineup like that?
Various Places in the New World
Hey, it's them!
You've finally started moving, Straw Hat.
Eustass "Captain" Kid
Kid Pirates - Captain
Bounty: 470 million belly
It's pointless to keep watching.
Besides, it's not like you to play arms dealer is it, Killer?
Killer
Kid Pirates - Combatant
Bounty: 200 million belly
Yeah, we all thought that bastard Trafalgar had lost his mind when he degraded himself
to be the government's lapdog, but it's no surprise that he had ulterior motives.
Is he trying to start something?
We can't afford to fall behind, we have to hurry!
Kid, please, let's be peaceable.
Shut up, I know that!
Scratchmen Apoo
Hey there, Captain Kid.
Basil Hawkins
You look as wound up as ever.
Scratchmen! What're you doing!?
You can't just wreck other people's hideouts like this!
Sorry, Captain! We couldn't stop them!
I was just making sure you didn't have any snipers!
On Air Pirates — Captain
Bounty: 350 million belly
You'd do the same if an enemy invited you.
See, Killer, this is why I told you not to bring these guys here!
Come on, take it easy, they're powerful men.
Every last one of you...
I'm gonna kill you all right now!
Oh, so that's how it is! I'm ready for ya!
Come on! Check it out!
Hawkins Pirates — Captain
Bounty: 320 million belly
This is foolish. I'm leaving.
Wait, Hawkins, don't give up so quickly!
You guys... that's enough!
You're here so that we can talk about an alliance between our three pirate crews!
Can't you guys at least discuss it!?
Counterattack?
Yeah, there's no sense in wasting any more time.
Let's finish this up quickly!
Are any of you able to set fire to things? It's fine if you can't though.
Franky can make fire and shoot beams.
I know! Why don't you melt these chains with your beam?
I need both of my hands in order to use Radical Beam.
Right now, all I can do...
is squeeze out a Coup de Boo from my ass.
Can you set fire to that warship down there on the right?
That's a simple task for me, bro! Let me handle it!
Franky...
Fireball!
The ship caught fire!
Run!
What's that Pacifista bastard doing? Is he crazy or just desperate?
It's no use struggling!
When the experiment is over I'll chop up your corpse and put the pieces to much better use!
I can't see the cage through all this smoke.
Captain-chan, are you alright!?
Smokey, is it smokey up there!?
Dumbass, Smokey's made of smoke!
Dammit, Trafalgar, the smoke's coming this way!
You're the one who did it.
You're the one who made me do it!
What're you playing at!?
Well then,
with all this smoke, Caesar won't be able to see us with the video transponder snails.
But it won't be long before we're exposed again.
How the hell did you manage to take off those Sea Stone handcuffs?
Well, I've had ordinary chains from the beginning.
What!?
It was easy to do with my ability.
Just how many months do you think I've been here?
I replaced a set of chains in the lab with normal ones in case there was ever a situation like this.
That way, if I was ever caught, I could switch them and avoid the Sea Stone ones.
I'm free!
Alright!
Don't shout, you fool!
Finally, finally free! I am finally free!
Right then, what shall I do with you?
You know a little bit too much.
Your fate rests with me.
You've already decided what to do anyway! Just get it over with!
You're an adult, what're you screaming like a little girl for!?
Please, just get these chains off me now! I'll do anything that you want!
What're you saying, Tashigi!? How can you even think of appealing to these pirates!?
We have to beg for our lives! If it takes groveling on our knees then so be it!
If we die here, then we'll be letting all our men die too!
Then Vice Admiral Vergo-
If we allow Vergo to do as he likes, then even more children will...
Looks like the woman is a little smarter than you are.
Little White Hunter, I have no obligation to save you at all,
but if sparing your lives will put Vergo at a disadvantage then that will benefit me.
However, you'd best forget everything you heard about me and Joker.
That is not a request. It's the condition for sparing your lives.
What's goin' on out there?
Alright! I'm finally out!
What're you doing!?
Hey, wait!
He'll just do what he wants if he's out of the cage!
It's not like that chain link stuff is made outta Sea Stone.
Hey! Trafal-guy!
How do I get inside?
Hey, Bro, I'd rather go and grab the Sunny.
Whatever.
What's that look for?
Run!
Even if we're running in this strange manner it's still catching up to us!
The dragon's getting further and further away!
We've gotta catch the damn thing and fly away now!
I can't go on!
Sanji-san! Don't give up!
It's no use, Nami-san's heart and lungs are about to give out!
My chest hurts!
My chest...
I caught him!
What kind of bizarre power up was that!?
That smoke is closing in!
With a color that creepy it's gonna be deadly poison for sure!
I'm sorry, Brownybeard, for asking you to carry us while you're so badly wounded.
No problem. It's only like carrying a couple of little dwarfs. Never mind that, I've gotta save my men!
We've gotta get the kids too! I hope they haven't had any candy yet!
Hey, what's that over there?
Look, there're people being chased by the gas.
A dragon?
The shutter opened!
This is an emergency!
The shutters have been raised!
Who touched the lever!?
Dammit! The G-5 marines are flooding in here!
Hey, over there!
It's Vice Admiral Smoker from the Navy's G-5!
One of the Seven Warlords of the Sea, Trafalgar Law!
And the pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
But, weren't they all captured by Master!?
Thank goodness, everyone got inside!
Now then, what to do about my heart?
This is gonna be cool!
I feel pathetic just being near you guys.
What's that?
Ouch!
Hang on a minute! Wait! Wait!
The shutter's closing!
Dammit, we just got here!
Open it! We've gotta get inside!
It's no use, we're gonna be locked out and killed by all the gas!
It's not too late, we're not dead yet!
Hey, Kin'emon, can you cut iron?
Nothing can hinder my sword!
Brownbeard, keep going like this!
They cut a hole in the shutter!
Hey, you're all here!
Luffy!
We're back!
Right! Let's go wild!
What've you done!?
This is bad!
It's great we made it inside, but the poison gas can get in too!
Are you guys serious!? You tryin' to kill us all along with you!?
Everyone, patch up that hole!
Otherwise we're done for!
It's over!
There's no longer anywhere for life to exist on Punk Hazard!
There're still great clouds of it everywhere.
Just one step outside in this stuff and you'd be done for.
What's it like, Brook?
Well, kinda like a world of death.
Just imagine if we hadn't patched up that hole.
It makes me shudder.
You make us shudder!
Right, good!
It's not good at all! You thoughtless bastards could've killed everyone here!
And we fixed the hole!
You pirates mess about even more than people say!
Give up now Straw Hat crew! And you too, pirate Brownbeard!
What!? Now it feels like we're backed into a corner! There's nowhere to run!
Is that even a problem?
Well, this is pretty normal for us.
They should just give up now.
Oh, they knew my name!
Oh, it's kicking off down there!
You two, don't get in the way of his crew and don't get in my way either, understand?
Yeah.
Hey, Trafal-guy, wait a moment!
Over here, over here!
Hurry up! Switch us back!
You don't have to!
Dammit! My dream is over!
I'm back! But, wait a moment...
Sanji-kun!?
Why is this coat different!? Did you take off my clothes!?
There's more to it than that...
Huh? My body?
This isn't damage from that punch just now.
Ah, yeah, Nami got your body pretty badly smashed up by Caesar.
What!?
I'm so glad it was my body that got battered instead.
I'm so proud of you! So very, very proud!
Everyone here, listen carefully!
Law!
This laboratory is totally surrounded by poison gas,
but there's a passage that bypasses the outside air and allows for escape directly to sea.
There's a giant door with R-66 written on it, that is the entrance to the passage out to sea.
I'm not a fan of mass murder, so I'll give you all two hours.
Any longer than that and I cannot guarantee the lives of anyone in this laboratory.
Will something happen to the lab?
It's a possibility. Right now, I just have to do what I have to do.
Ah, alright then.
Robin, I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
G-5!
Smokey!
There're children in this laboratory that were kidnapped two years ago!
We need to take them back and then head for door R-66!
If what he said is true then there's a port straight ahead from there.
We'll steal a ship and escape from Punk Hazard!
Yeah! Let's go!
Let's say goodbye to this island!
The children...
Guys, let's split up and find the children!
Then we can get every last one of them safely into the passageway! It's R-66!
Zoro, you're not allowed to be alone!
Wait for me, Momonosuke! I'm coming for you!
Alright, I understand.
Thanks! Right then!
Just you wait, Caesar! You're not gonna stop me breathing again!
I'm gonna batter you and take you hostage!
Tashigi, I need you to lead those G-5 idiots now.
Where're you going, Smoker-san?
Not to face Vergo!?
I won't forgive that guy!
The law doesn't work in situations like this, Tashigi!
I'll do it myself. He's underestimated the Navy!
Please, let me come too!
His... Vergo is insanely strong!
What if something went wrong!?
Who's gonna protect our men? Help those idiots and the children escape.
Smoker-san.
What? Seriously? Luffy already got beaten by Caesar?
Yeah, we weren't prepared and we wound up suffocating, too.
That bastard is a real pain! Since he's made outta gas he can suck the oxygen out of the air!
We got knocked out by those yetis, too!
This is not good.
Huh?
This is not good at all!
What were those two years for!?
Well, come on, we're both alive so-
This isn't a joke!
If we drop our guard beyond here there'll be no forgiveness!
Hey, Luffy!
Zoro?
Stop messing around! From here on out this is the New World!
He's pretty tough on himself.
Yeah, sorry! I won't drop my guard again!
It's Straw Hat!
I dunno what he's doing, just take him out!
Rubber...
UFO!
I'm going ahead!
I said be more serious!
Get outta my way!
Let's go!
Translation, Hattori
Initial timing, Hattori
Timing, Galaxy 9000
Quality checking, Sewil
Soundtracking, MaideV and Halee
Raw providing, OPC-Raws
Editing, Sewil